제작 blog.naver.com/incusx
이유는 모르겠지만 오늘은 정말 좋은 날일꺼 같아!
I don't know why but today seems like it's gonna be a great day!
공기 중의 무언가가 마치 모든 게 내 뜻대로 될것만 같은 기분이 들게 해줘
There's something in the air that makes me feel like things are gonna go my way
새들은 짹짹 지저귀고, 해는 밝게 빛나네!
The birds are chirping tweedly-deet, the sun is shining bright!
나는 까불며 뛰어다니고, 생기가 돋아나는데
There's a skip in my step, a pip in my pep
이유는 뭔지 모르겠어!
and I don't know why!
안녕 집배원 친구, 전처나 내 아이들에게서 편지 온 거 없어?
Hey there mailman friend, any letters from my ex-wife or the kids?
없어
No
환상적인 소식이야!
Fantastic news!
아름다운 날은 내 기분을 아주 행복하게 해줘서 내 얼굴이 마비될 거 같아!
Wonderful day makes me feel so happy that my face is numb!
내 심장은 미친듯이 쿵쾅쿵쾅 뛰네!
My heart is racing along barapa pampam!
갈 곳도 많고 만날 사람도 많아, 나는 이제 직장에서 짤렸으니까!
So many places and people to meet, now that I've lost my job!
그리고 그들은, " 젊은이, 모든 게 다 잘될거야' 라고 하겠지
They say "Young man, the world's your oyster"
이봐! 내 몸에서 씨발 손 떼라고!
Hey! Hey get the fuck off me!
싫어! 좆나게 싫다고!
No! Fuck No!
잠시 만요...
Just give me second.
이유는 모르겠지만 오늘은 정말 좋은 날일꺼 같아!
I don't know why but today seems like it's gonna be a great day!
랄랄라 어쩌고저쩌고 나는 우리 아이들과 더 많은 시간을 보내야 될거 같아!
Lalala blah blah blah blah I should spend more time with my kids!
현재를 즐겨야해,  오늘을 즐기기 위해,
It's carpe diem, gotta seize the day,
나는 스페인으로 가서 황소 달리기에 참가할 꺼야
I'm gonna move to Spain and run with the bulls
그리고 내 아내랑 상사랑 아이들이랑 부모님은
And my wife and boss and kids and parents will say
"데니스, 우리가 잘 못했단다." 라고 하겠지.
"We were wrong about you Dennis"
안녕, 데니스!
Hey Dennis!
그거 내 이름인데!
That's my name!
황소달리기에 진짜 참가할 꺼야?
Are you really gonna run with the bulls?
내가 왜 해야 하는데?
Why would I do that?
왜냐면 네가 한다고 했잖아!
Cause you said you were gonna!
이봐, 정신 차려, 그 소리 한지 3일도 더 된거 같잖아,
Come on man, that was like three days ago
아니면 진짜 그랬나?
or was it?
오늘 뭔가가 내 기분을 자유롭고 좋게 만들어주네
Something today makes me feel fine and fancy-free
대부분의 바다는 여전히 탐험이 되지 않았고,
Much of the ocean is still unexplored,
나는 어떻게 이 나무에 올라온 걸까?
how did I get up in this tree?
지금 나는 여기 있고, 지금 나는 저기 있고
Now I'm over here, now I'm over there
지금 나는 이 자식 밑에 있고, 지금 나는 다시 나무에 있네
Now I'm under this dude, now I'm back in the tree
나는 지금 나의 완전 베프들과 무대 뒤에 있지
Now I'm hanging out backstage with my very best friends
알렉 볼드윈이랑 톰 페티야!
Alec Baldwin and Tom Petty!
씨발 놈아 꺼져버려!
Get the fuck out of here!
뭐?
What?
당장.
Now.
톰!
Tom!
왜 쟤들이 날 싫어하는 걸까?
Why would they diss me?
나는 쟤들을 베프라고 생각하고 있었는데!
I thought they were my homies!
어떤 문제든 해결할 수 있어, 우리는 배고픔을 채우고 병을 치료할 수 있어
Any problem is solvable, we can feed the hungry and cure disease
하지만 그딴건 전부 엄청난 시간낭비일뿐야
But all of that would be a huge waste of time
왜냐면 우리는 매트릭스 안에 살고 있으니까
because we live in the matrix.
왜 저래?
What is wrong with him?
저놈 약 빨았네
He's on drugs.
아.
Oh.